Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Labor and Radicalism Photograph Collection PHOTOS.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Rand School - Folder 2: Classroom Scenes (Box 7, Folder 359)
- Rand School - Folder 3: Class Photos (Box 7, Folder 360)
- Rand School - Folder 4: Group Portraits (Box 8, Folder 361)
- Rand School - Folder 4: Group Portraits (Box Shared Tamiment OS006, Folder 1)
- Rand School - Folder 5: Bookstore (Box 8, Folder 362)
- Rand School - Folder 6: People's House and Misc. Rand School (Box 8, Folder 363)
- Rand School - Folder 7: Tamiment Library: Reception for Mayor of W. Berlin, Willy Brandt (Box 8, Folder 364)
- Rand School - Folder 8: Tamiment Library: Tamiment Reception (Box 8, Folder 365)
- Rand School - Folder 9: Tamiment Library: Tamiment Library Reception (Box 8, Folder 366)
- Rand School - Folder 10: Tamiment Library: Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 356)
- Rand School - Folder 11: Building (Box Shared Tamiment OS006, Folder 4)
- Rand School - Folder 11: Building (Box 8, Folder 357)
- Rand School - Folder 12: Unidentified Portraits (Box 8, Folder 358)
- Rand School - Folder 13: Oversize, undated (Box Shared Tamiment OS003, Folder 6)
- Rand School - Folder 13: Oversize (Box Shared Tamiment XOS002)
- Randolph, A. Phillip (Box 8, Folder 367)
- Randolph, A. Philip: A. Philip Randolph Educational Fund (Box 8, Folder 585)
- Rauschenberg, Walter (Box 8, Folder 368)
- Reagan, Ronald (Box 8, Folder 369)
- Red International of Labor Unions, Executive Bureau (Box 8, Folder 370)
- Reed, John (Box 8, Folder 371)
- Renaudel, Pierre (Box 8, Folder 372)
- Renner, Karl (Box 8, Folder 373)
- Retail Clerks International Association, 1967 (Box Shared Tamiment XOS001)
- Reuther, Walter P. (Box 8, Folder 374)
- Reynolds, Stephen Marion (Box 8, Folder 374.1)
- Rillieux, Norbert (Box 8, Folder 375)
- Rivera, Diego (Box Shared Tamiment OS003, Folder 7)
- Rivera, Diego (Box 8, Folder 376)
- Roberts, Lillian (Box 8, Folder 377)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 1: Portraits (Box 8, Folder 378)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 2: Contact Sheets (Box 12, Folder 570)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 3:Othello, Stratford-on-Avon (Box 12, Folder 571)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 4:At the Front, Spainish Civil War (Box 12, Folder 572)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 5: Rallies, Meetings, and Performances (Box 12, Folder 573)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 6: Award Ceremonies (Box 12, Folder 574)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 7: Events Dedicated to (Box 12, Folder 575)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 8: On Trips to Eastern Europe (Soviet Union and East Germany) (Box 12, Folder 576)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 9: With Others (Box 12, Folder 577)
- Robeson, Paul - Folder 10: Negatives (Box 12, Folder 578)
- Rocker, Rudolph and Milly (Box 8, Folder 379)
- Rodriguez, William E. (Box 8, Folder 380)
- Roosevelt, Eleanor [at Local 2, United Storeworkers, District 65] (Box 8, Folder 381)
- Rose, Ernestine (Box 8, Folder 382)
- Rosenberg, Elmer (Box 8, Folder 383)
- Rosenberg, Ethel and Julius (Box 8, Folder 384)
- Ross, Edward Alsworth (Box 8, Folder 385)
- Rubin, Jay (Box 8, Folder 386)
- Russell, Bertrand (Box 8, Folder 387)
- Rustin, Bayard (Box 8, Folder 388)
- Ruthenberg, Charles Emil (Box 8, Folder 389)
- Sacco and Vanzetti (Box 8, Folder 390)
- Sandburg, Carl (Box 8, Folder 391)
- Sanger, Margaret (Box 8, Folder 392)
- Sanial, Lucien (Box 8, Folder 393)
- Sasaki, Kohzo (Box 8, Folder 394)
- Scheidermann, Philipp (Box 8, Folder 395)
- Schneiderman, Rose (Box 8, Folder 396)
- Scotto, Anthony (Box 8, Folder 397)
- Scottsboro (Box 8, Folder 398)
- Seger, Gerhart (Box 8, Folder 399)
- Seitz (Mayor of Vienna) (Box 8, Folder 400)
- Senior, Clarence (Box 8, Folder 401)
- Shachtman, Max (Box 8, Folder 402)
- Shadid, Michael (Box 8, Folder 403)
- Shapler, Joseph (Box 8, Folder 404)
- Shaw, George Bernard (Box 8, Folder 405)
- Shaw, Lemuel (Box 8, Folder 406)
- Sheet Metal Workers - Local 28 (Box 8, Folder 407)
- Shiplocoff, A.I. (Box 8, Folder 408)
- Simons, A. M. (Box 8, Folder 409)
- Sinclair, Upton (Box 8, Folder 410)
- Singer, Franz (Box 8, Folder 411)
- Slovak Workers Society (Box 8, Folder 412)
- Sobell, Morton (Box 8, Folder 413)
- Social Democratic Federation (Box 8, Folder 414)
- Social Democratic League (Box 8, Folder 415)
- Social Democratic Party (Box 8, Folder 416)
- Social Democratic Party (Box Shared Tamiment OS006, Folder 2)
- Socialist Party (Box 9, Folder 417)
- Socialist Party - California (Box 9, Folder 418)
- Socialist Party - Michigan (Box 9, Folder 419)
- Socialist Party - New York (Box 9, Folder 420)
- Socialist Party - New York (Flat-file-folder 7, Tray 2, Flat-file-folder 9, Tray 3)
- Socialist Party - Pennsylvania (Box 9, Folder 421)
- Socialist Party - US, May 1920, May 1936, undated (Flat-file-folder 5, Tray 2)
- Socialist Party - US (Box Shared Tamiment OS006, Folder 2-3)
- Socialist Party - US (Box 9, Folder 422)
- Socialist Party - US (Flat-file-folder 6, Tray 2)
- Socialist Party - Workers of the World Unite, Undated (Flat-file-folder 1, Tray 1)
- Societe Cooperative Ouvriere de Bruxelles (Box 9, Folder 423)
- Solomon, Charles (Box 9, Folder 424)
- Sorge, (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box 9, Folder 425)
- Sotherton, Alice Hyneman (Mrs. Holland) (Box 9, Folder 426)
- Spanish Civil War (Box 9, Folder 427)
- Stalin, Josef (Box 9, Folder 428)
- Stanton, Elizabeth Cady (Box 9, Folder 429)
- State, County and Municipal Workers of America (SCMWA) (Box 9, Folder 587)
- Statue of Liberty (Box 9, Folder 430)
- Steamfitter (Box 9, Folder 431)
- Stedman, Seyomour (Box 12, Folder 562)
- Stedman, Seyomour (Box Shared Tamiment OS006, Folder 1)
- Steinmetz, Charles Proteus (Box 9, Folder 432)
- Stevens, Uriah S. (Box 9, Folder 433)
- Stevenson, Adlai (Box 9, Folder 434)
- Stokes, J.G. Phelps (Box 9, Folder 435)
- Stokes, Rose Pastor (Box 9, Folder 436)
- Stone, Lucy (Box 9, Folder 437)
- Strikes - Clothing Workers (Box 9, Folder 438)
- Strikes - Dressmakers (Box 9, Folder 439)
- Strikes - Miners (Box 9, Folder 440)
- Strikes - Miners - Ludlow, CO. (Box 9, Folder 441)
- Strikes - Pennsylvania (Box 9, Folder 442)
- Strikes - Public Workers (Box 9, Folder 583)
- Strikes - Railroads (Box 9, Folder 443)
- Strikes - Shoemakers - Lynn, MA (Box 9, Folder 444)
- Strikes - Steel (Box 9, Folder 445)
- Strikes - Textile Workers (Box 9, Folder 446)
- Strikes - Textile Workers - Lawrence, MA (Box 9, Folder 447)
- Strikes - Textile Workers - Passaic, NJ (Box 9, Folder 448)
- Strikes - Textile Workers - Paterson, NJ (Box 10, Folder 449)
- Strikes - US (Box 10, Folder 450)
- Strikes - White Collar Workers (Miscellaneous) (Box 12, Folder 584)
- Strong, Anna Louise (Box 10, Folder 451)
- Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee (Box 10, Folder 452)
- Stulberg, Louis (Box 10, Folder 453)
- Stump (Mayor of Reading, PA) (Box 10, Folder 454)
- Susman, Bill (Box 10, Folder 455)
- Sweatshops (Box 10, Folder 456)
- Sweeney, John (Box 10, Folder 457)
- Sweet Case (Box 10, Folder 458)
- Sylvis, William H. (Box 10, Folder 459)
- Tamiment - Camp Tamiment (Box 10, Folder 460)
- Tamiment Institute (Box 10, Folder 461)
- Tamiment Institute - Tamiment Book Award:1956 (Box 10, Folder 462)
- Tamiment Institute - Tamiment Book Award? 1960's (Box 10, Folder 463)
- Tamiment Institute - Tamiment College Essay Contest (Box 10, Folder 464)
- Tamiment Institute -Tamiment Book Award:1953 (Box 10, Folder 465)
- Tandler, Julius (Box 10, Folder 466)
- Tanner, Jack (Box 10, Folder 467)
- Tarkak (Box 10, Folder 468)
- Taxi, Rank and File Coalition, Local 3036 - NYC (Box 10, Folder 469)
- Tenayuca, Emma (Box 10, Folder 470)
- Thirty Hour Week (Box 10, Folder 471)
- Thomas, Norman (Box 10, Folder 472)
- Thompson, Carl D. (Box 10, Folder 473)
- Tobenkin, Paul (Box 10, Folder 474)
- Trachtenburg (Box 10, Folder 475)
- Trade Unions - Coal Miners - United Mine Workers of America (Box 10, Folder 476)
- Trade Unions - Communication Workers of America (Box 10, Folder 477)
- Trade Unions - Hospital Workers - 1199, National Union of Hospital and Health Care workers (Box 10, Folder 478)
- Trade Unions - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (Box 10, Folder 479)
- Trade Unions - International Ladies Garment Workers Union (Box 10, Folder 480)
- Trade Unions - Needle Workers Industrial Union, 1929 (Box Shared Tamiment XOS001)
- Trade Unions - Newspaper Guild - Chicago Strike, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 563)
- Trade Unions - Office Workers - Bookkeepers, Stenographers, Accountants Union, AFL (Box 10, Folder 481)
- Trade Unions - Office Workers - United Office and Professional Workers of America - CIO (Box 10, Folder 482)
- Trade Unions - State, County, and Municipal Workers of America (SCMWA) (Box Shared Tamiment OS006, Folder 1)
- Trade Unions - State, County, and Municipal Workers of America (SCMWA) (Box 12, Folder 587)
- Trade Unions - Transport Workers Union (Box 10, Folder 483)
- Traubel, Horace (Box 10, Folder 484)
- Travellick, Richard F. (Box 10, Folder 485)
- Trenton 6 (Box 10, Folder 486)
- Tresca, Carlo (Box 12, Folder 564)
- Triangle Fire (Box 10, Folder 487)
- Triangle Fire (Reproductions), undated (Box Shared Tamiment OS003)
- Trotsky, Leon (Box 11, Folder 488)
- Tucker, Benjamin R. (Box 11, Folder 489)
- Tunnelworkers Local 147 (Box 11, Folder 490)
- Turati, Philippo (Box 11, Folder 491)
- Twining, Luella (Box 11, Folder 492)
- UFT-Local 3882 (NYU) (Box 11, Folder 493)
- Unemployed Movement (Box Shared Tamiment OS003, Folder 9)
- Unemployed Movement (Box 11, Folder 494)
- Unidentified Photographs (Box 11, Folder 495)
- Unidentified Portraits (Box 11, Folder 496)
- Unidentified Portraits (Box Shared Tamiment XOS002, Folder 1)
- Union Label (Box 11, Folder 497)
- Union Square (Box 11, Folder 498)
- United Auto Workers (Box 11, Folder 499)
- United Garment Workers of America (Box 11, Folder 500)
- United Hatters (Box 11, Folder 501)
- United Labor Party (19th Century) (Box 11, Folder 502)
- United States Naval Training Station-Great Lakes, Illinois, Jan 19, 1944 (Box Shared Tamiment OS005, Folder 5)
- United States Women's Bureau, Jan 20, 1925 (Flat-file-folder 6, Tray 3)
- United Steel Workers (Box 11, Folder 503)
- United Transportation Union, Cleveland, OH (Box 11, Folder 504)
- Untermann, Ernest (Box 11, Folder 505)
- USSR (Box 11, Folder 506)
- Utility Workers (Box 11, Folder 507)
- Vail, Charles H. (Box 11, Folder 508)
- Vaillant, Edouard (Box 11, Folder 509)
- Van Arsdale, Harry (Jr.) (Box 11, Folder 510)
- Van Kleeck, Mary (Box 11, Folder 586)
- Vanderveer, George (Box 11, Folder 511)
- Vandervelde, Emile (Box 11, Folder 512)
- Vladeck, B. Charney (Box 11, Folder 513)
- Vladeck, B. Charney (Box Shared Tamiment OS006, Folder 1)
- Vorse, Mary Heaton (Box 11, Folder 514)
- Wagner Family, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_c4d80cbe763375d6bef24bcf9df9ea3a)
- Wagner, Robert F. (Senator) (Box 11, Folder 515)
- Wagner, Robert F. (Senator) (Box Shared Tamiment OS003, Folder 8)
- Wagner, Robert F. (Senator) (Flat-file-folder 2)
- Wagner, Robert F. Jr. (Box 11, Folder 516)
- Wagner, Robert F. III (1944-1993) (Box 12, Folder 565)
- Waldheim Cemetery, Chicago, IL (Box 11, Folder 517)
- Waldman, Louis (Box 11, Folder 518)
- Wallace, Henry (Box 11, Folder 519)
- Wanhope, Joshua (Box 11, Folder 520)
- War (Box 11, Folder 521)
- Ward, Lester F. (Box 11, Folder 522)
- Warren, Fred D. (Box 11, Folder 523)
- Washington (State) - Centralia (Box 11, Folder 524)
- Washington (State) - Montesano Chahalis County (Box 11, Folder 525)
- Wattes, Florence (Box 11, Folder 526)
- Webb, Sidney (Box 11, Folder 527)
- Weizman, Chaim (Box 11, Folder 528)
- Western Federation of Miners (Box 11, Folder 529)
- Whitman, Walt (Box 11, Folder 530)
- Wilson, Lilith Martin (Box 11, Folder 531)
- Wise, Stephen S. (Box 11, Folder 532)
- Women - Employment (Box 11, Folder 533)
- Women - Trade Unions (Box 11, Folder 534)
- Women and Labor (Box 11, Folder 535)
- Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (WILPF), Jan 2, 1925, undated (Box 12, Folder 588)
- Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (WILPF) (Flat-file-folder 9, Tray 4)
- Women's Peace Party WWII (Box 11, Folder 536)
- Women's Trade Union League (Flat-file-folder 3, Tray 1)
- Women's Union Label League, Local 197, San Diego, CA (Box 11, Folder 537)
- Wood, G.W. (Chico, Montana) (Box 11, Folder 538)
- Workers - Glaziers (Box 12, Folder 566)
- Workers - Lace Weavers (Box 12, Folder 539)
- Workers - Lumber Industry (Box 12, Folder 567)
- Workers - Miners (Box 12, Folder 540)
- Workers - Print Shops (Box 12, Folder 568)
- Workers - Sign Painters (Box 12, Folder 541)
- Workers - Textile (Box 12, Folder 542)
- Worksites (Box 12, Folder 543)
- World War II (Box 12, Folder 544)
- World War II - Civilians (Box 12, Folder 545)
- Wright, Clyde (Box 12, Folder 545.1)
- Yellow Dog Contract (Box 12, Folder 546)
- Young, Arthur H.- Caricaturist/ cartoonist (Box 12, Folder 547)
- YPSL (Young People's Socialist League) (Box 12, Folder 548)
- Yurick, Sol (Box 12, Folder 569)
- Zaritsky, Max - Folder 1 (Box 12, Folder 549)
- Zaritsky, Max - Folder 2 (Box 12, Folder 550)
- Zetkin, Clara (Box 12, Folder 551)
- Glass Negatives, 1903, undated (Box 15, Box 16)
- Glass Lantern Slides of Puerto Rico, 1902-1926 (Box 17, Box 18)
- Workmen's Circle group portrait, 10th Convention, 1910 (Box Shared Tamiment 032)